olx.com.my 2018-06-27

# About Mudah - Mudah.my

Mudah.my.Sdn. Bhd. (" **Mudah** ") is committed to protecting your personal information and will take the relevant measures to safeguard your personal information in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2010. This Privacy Policy (" **Policy** ") sets out how we use and protect the information you give us. This Policy only applies to personal information of individuals that are processed for commercial transactions.

## Collection of Personal Information

We do not collect any personal information or personally identifiable information when you visit our website Mudah.my, all its official Android / iOS app and all related sub-sites (" **Site** ") unless you choose to provide that information to us.

We may also collection information that personally identifies you if you choose to submit your personal information for the various purposes made available on our Site. We will then serve you with a personal data protection notice (" **Notice** ") to confirm your consent and notify you on our processing of your personal information. The processing of your personal information will be done in accordance with all applicable laws.  
Any information we collection from you may be used in any of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience on our Site
  * To improve our Site and services provided to you
  * To process any transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of providing our services to you.
  * To send period emails  
The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates from the Site that could be relevant to you, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.   
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
  * To administer our contest, promotion, survey, event or other Site feature or activity

## Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Mudah may disclose your personal information to the following parties (including those overseas) for the purposes stated above:

  * agents and service providers who provide services relating to the purposes of which the personal information is collected including data processing services;
  * any person, who is under a duty of confidentiality who has undertaken the responsibility to keep such information confidential; and
  * Mudah's related and associate companies and affiliates.

We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent. However, we may disclose your personal information if required by law or in good faith, if such action is necessary to comply with any law enforcement agency requirements, court orders or legal processes.

## Access and Update of Your Personal Information

If you would like to access, update or correct your personal information, you may contact us at dpo@mudah.my. Any request to access or correct personal information may be subject to a fee and will be bound by data protection laws in Malaysia.

## Changes to this Policy

Mudah may review and change this Policy from time to time to reflect changes in the law, our business practices, processes or structure. While it is not generally feasible to notify you of the changes to this Policy, the latest version of this Policy will be available on our website. This policy is not a contract, nor does it suggest any obligation on our part with another party.
